<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>/en/accueil</title>
    <link>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on /en/accueil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 14:25:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geishagroove.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Medias</title>
      <link>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/medias/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 11:04:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/medias/</guid>
      <description>      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>À propos de Geisha Groove</title>
      <link>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 11:03:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Geisha Groove Function band is:  A female collective that musically animates your private or public events; weddings, birthdays, Corporate Events, Receptions, etc… Musical craft - woman ship and plenty of gigging experience Professionalism and talent A rich repertoire bound to satisfy listener of all ages Quality sound (high-quality gear, sound-system and instruments)  Here are the many formulas you can choose from:  Acoustic Cocktail Set ( 45min to 1hour 15 min) - Duo, Trio or Quartet Amplified Cocktail Set ( 45min to 1hour 15 min) - Duo, Trio or Quartet Instrumental Jazz Set ( 45min to 1 hour 30 min) - Duo Trio or Quartet Vocal Jazz Set ( 45 min to 1 hour) - Trio or Quartet Party Set ( 45 min to 1 hour 30 min) - Trio or Quartet Traditional Music of Reunion Island a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/accueil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geishagroove.github.io/en/accueil/</guid>
      <description>accueil.fr.md&amp;mdash; title: &amp;ldquo;Accueil&amp;rdquo; date: 2019-10-29T11:03:32+01:00
draft: false Geisha groove is unique experience in its own right. Its a female soul/funk power house with quality musical arrangement and tasty contemporary interpretation of our favourite classics. These three excellent musicians are bound to get you on the dance floor, they’re mediterranean and tropical origins, Corsica, Reunion Island and Lantau Island emerge in the warmth and the groove of their live shows. The trio proposes a large palette of possibilities ranging from smooth cocktail sets to punchier party band vibes, encompassing full drums, bass and keyboards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>